It is good that
secondly, heartiest greetings of Diwali to all of you.
So today in this video we will talk about
some of our important fixes for tomorrow's Muhurat trading
and if you want, you
can do these through Android app or on position basis. So let's start
if we talk about how
we saw in the market today. So here
in the soil, properties
56001 subscribe my channel, after short covering,
we
now talk about it, it had
put 30 and later due to some reason,
we
got 10 in the market and here you
can see two Jhalars here for selling pressure,
which is going to take tension of 1 hour of Muhurat trading of many houses, so that
we are going to
straighten the investment or short term deposit receipt stocks,
so let's see all those staff,
so the first name that comes is this,
friends, as you all know that
Garlic Dhanteras was celebrated here with great pomp
and it happened on the same day here and
I was reading a report in India, in it it was written that some
gold should come here due to stunt  It has been done
because it is clear from this that if the
transactions increase then you will get a good demand from the company
which is financing gold loan to bluetooth.
So today we have written a similar seal
here, after being a shooting stock, the
oil question that came in it has become a
company in the last role and
if you consider it, then from here above 30,
you will definitely show you a side for the next few days
that the buying in the solution
continues for a few days, so you
can consider it for the next 520, okay, if
you drink it in different areas of tomorrow,
you will also
get an option to make divine profit and in that case you should look more at carat
leave,
after this now let's talk about India's
instructor story, here the
name of last metro comes at the top and here
experts have seen development and gear
are the listed stocks within these fruits and
in the last metro, which
we saw today in the off side, above it, from here a
very big fragrance is seen  Chances increase because
we have today seen a fresh all-time high on
this platform. It has
made a high above 90 and due to the market which was able to
return, Arrowroot
1089 was also seen here. The device
girlfriend is not 30, see that it happens, then a K is
given in it and at least
if you are considering it as a short term deposit
for the phase, on the return of the side
in the market, the traffic in these upside returns
is 1958 twelfth class room
and this is the third one in our list.
Before watching it, if you are on this channel and
you like to see such updates, then
definitely ask for your support by picking up this channel
with your like and subscribe button so
that we know what kind of updates you
like to see. If you are watching this
important video right now, then it will be
very important for business and event investors,
so
you should only watch it, the third one which
comes is SBI today, there is only
one in the talk after the viewers end.  It was placed around 500
Tk and after going above it,
we get to see a slot of around 700 in Bank Nifty,
so because of this we
saw a close loop above 530, if we consider its border to, then even now on a from
and back
side we get to see that if
possible, when I opened Kalyan,
you can clear the market in Saffron, in that in
easy, you can get
electrical up to 550 and 3560
and if you want to cancel on this channel basis, then
method want to fix,
you do not need at least five thirty plus here,
after this if we give
our fourth and last point then it is
SBI card and above this we should bar
because at
present the use of Sweet card
on online portals like Amazon, the stock which is active,
its use has increased a lot in some,
because traditional cards are available,
considering this, here you will get to see
some interest in the stock in its current
form, so like and just
stop and stand on the penis, then your
What position can you do, please take the pipe, I have
also appointed the method for it very easily,
you will
definitely see the website of photo impression, that's all for today
's video, if you like the video then
please like and share, so we will meet
in the next video, till then dhota his heart
and definition in English happened
that a
[Music]